const question = [
    {
    question:'Where do the guys in TBBT work',
    options:['caltech','MIT','A private research facility','A pharmaceutical company'],
    answer:'MIT'
    },
    {
    question:"Where is the gang's apartment?",
    options:['glendale','pasadena','downtown la','burbank'],
    answer:'pasadena'
    },
    {
    question:"Where did Howard go to school?",
    options:['caltech','MIT','stanford','cambridge'],
    answer:'MIT'
    },
    {
    question:"How did Sheldon and Amy meet?",
    options:['Through friends of Amy','thiough work','a chance meeting','through a dating site'],
    answer:'through a dating site'
    },
    {
    question:"How did Howard and Bernadette meet?",
    options:['dating site','his mother set him up','Penny set them up','speed dating'],
    answer:'Penny set them up'
    },
    {
    question:"What does Stuart do for a living?",
    options:['At a movie theater','A professional artist','Owns a comic book store','writer'],
    answer:'Owns a comic book store'
    },
    {
    question:"Which magazine was Raj in?",
    options:['variety','people','scientific american','instyle'],
    answer:'people'
    },
    {
    question:"Where was Penny a waitress?",
    options:['The Cheesecake Factory','boston pizza','olive garden','outback steakhouse'],
    answer:'The Cheesecake Factory'
    },
    {
    question:"Where did Penny and Leonard get married?",
    options:["penny's hometown",'pasadena','las vegas','leonard hometown'],
    answer:'las vegas'
    },
    {
    question:"What is the name of their geologist friend?",
    options:['bert','barry','peter','john'],
    answer:'bert'
    },
    {
    question:"What was the name of Kripke's robot?",
    options:['The Kripke Killer','the fighting kripke','the kripke crippler','the battle tank'],
    answer:'the kripke crippler'
    },
    {
    question:"How did Sheldon meet Wil Wheaton?",
    options:['At a comic convention','at a comic book store game tournament','At the Cheesecake Factory','At work, where Wil was studying for a role'],
    answer:'at a comic book store game tournament'
    },
    {
    question:"How does Sheldon know he's not crazy?",
    options:['his mother had him tested',"he's too smart to be crazy","he doesn't believe in crazy",'crazy is for other people'],
    answer:'his mother had him tested'
    },
    {
    question:"What is the name of Sheldon's webseries?",
    options:['word with nerds','sheldon explains trains','fun with flag','science for sillies'],
    answer:'fun with flag'
    },
    {
    question:"What was the name of Raj's dermatologist girlfriend?",
    options:['rebecca','emily','jennifer','claire'],
    answer:'emily'
    }
]

module.exports = question